A Guide to the Hao Wang papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA274
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Manuscripts, Notes, and Notebooks, 3
  - Mathematics 234 and 287 Notes and Manuscripts (Box 90, Folder 1320)
  - "Mathematics as a Numerical Language" by Errett Bishop and "Comments on the Foundations of Set Theory" by Paul J. Cohen (Box 90, Folder 1321)
  - "Mathematics, Science and Ontology" by Thomas Tymoczko (Box 91, Folder 1322)
  - Mechanical Procedures, from "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 91, Folder 1323)
  - "The Mechanization of Mathematical Arguments", Includes: “Machines as an Aid to Theorem-Proving” (Box 91, Folder 1324)
  - "Mechanization of Theorem-Proving in Elementary Geometry" (Box 91, Folder 1325)
  - Merrifield (Box 91, Folder 1326)
  - Metalogic, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 1327)
  - "Mind Brain Machine" (Box 91, Folder 1328)
  - "Mind, Machine, and Mathematics" (Box 91, Folder 1329)
  - Marvin Minsky (Box 92, Folder 1330)
  - D. Mirimanoff (Box 92, Folder 1331)
  - MIT Press - Royalty Statements (Box 92, Folder 1332)
  - William J. Mitchell (Box 92, Folder 1333)
  - Modern Development...int he Light of Philosophy, Gödel-related (Box 92, Folder 1334)
  - Shaw-kwei Moh (Box 92, Folder 1335)
  - Mongré/Bollert (Box 92, Folder 1336)
  - Edward F. Moore (Box 92, Folder 1337)
  - "The Moscow Lecture" (Box 93, Folder 1338)
  - MR - "Mathematical Realism - A Zone of Convergence with Gödel" (Box 93, Folder 1339)
  - MSS, 1968-1970 (Box 93, Folder 1340)
  - Albert A. Mullin (Box 93, Folder 1341)
  - Music, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 1342)
  - Wayne C. Myrvold and Abner Shimony (Box 93, Folder 1343)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Grant Application, Jaakko Hintikka and Judson Webb (Box 93, Folder 1344)
  - "New Directions" (Box 93, Folder 1345)
  - "The Non-Finitizability of Impredicative Principles" (Box 93, Folder 1346)
  - "A Note on the Sum of an Infinite Series" by Palle Yourgrau (Box 93, Folder 1347)
  - Notebook, 1950 (Box 94, Folder 1348)
  - Notebook, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 1349)
  - Notebook, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 1350)
  - Notebook, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 1351)
  - Notebook, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 1352)
  - Notebook, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 1353)
  - Notebook, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1354)
  - Notebook, 1970? (Box 95, Folder 1355)
  - Notebook, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 1356)
  - Notebook, A.M. 231, 2 copies (Box 95, Folder 1357)
  - Notebook, Applied Mathematics 231 and 234 (1 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 1358)
  - Notebook, Applied Mathematics 231 and 234 (2 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 1359)
  - Notebook, Applied Mathematics 231 and 234 [Copy 2] (1 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 1360)
  - Notebook, Applied Mathematics 231 and 234 [Copy 2] (2 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 1361)
  - Notebook, Applied Mathematics 231 and 234 [Copy 3] (1 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 1362)
  - Notebook, Applied Mathematics 231 and 234 [Copy 3] (2 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 1363)
  - Notebook, "Bar Theorem/Fan Theorem" (Box 96, Folder 1364)
  - Notebook, Bell Telephone Laboratories (Box 96, Folder 1365)
  - Notebook, Bell Telephone Laboratories (Box 96, Folder 1366)
  - Notebook, Bell Telephone Laboratories (Box 96, Folder 1367)
  - Notebook, Bell Telephone Laboratories (Box 97, Folder 1368)
  - Notebook, Bell Telephone Laboratories (Box 97, Folder 1369)
  - Notebook, "Bishop's Book" (Box 97, Folder 1370)
  - Notebook, "Constructivity" (Box 97, Folder 1371)
  - Notebook, "Conversations with Gödel", 1971-1972 (Box 97, Folder 1372)
  - Notebook, "Conversations with Gödel", 1976-1978 (Box 97, Folder 1373)
  - Notebook, Conversations with Gödel: A New Attempt, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 1374)
  - Notebook, Decision Problems (Box 97, Folder 1375)
  - Notebook, "Decision Problems", 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1376)
  - Notebook, "From Mathematics to Philosophy, Knowledge and Logic" (Box 98, Folder 1377)
  - Notebook, "From Mathematics to Philosophy/Knowledge and Logic", 1971-1972 (Box 98, Folder 1378)
  - Notebook, Gödel, April-August 1972 (Box 98, Folder 1379)
  - Notebook, Gödel, 1972-1978 (Box 98, Folder 1380)
  - Notebook, Gödel, 1986-1987 (Box 98, Folder 1381)
  - Notebook, Gödel Manuscript (Box 98, Folder 1382)
  - Notebook, Gödel, "A Reconstruction of the Conversations" (Box 98, Folder 1383)
  - Notebook, "GTR" (Box 99, Folder 1384)
  - Notebook, "Hao Wang", 1967 (Box 99, Folder 1385)
  - Notebook, "Hrbacek, Martin" (Box 99, Folder 1386)
  - Notebook, "The Ideal World" (Box 99, Folder 1387)
  - Notebook [Label in Chinese, by Hao Wang], 1947 (Box 99, Folder 1388)
  - Notebook, Lectures on Logic and Mathematics, Includes: “Logical Structure of Mathematics, Orientation Lectures, October 1968” “Formal Logic” “Minds and Computers” “Mind, Machine and Mathematics” “The Unity of Knowledge, January 1968” “Forcing” “Constructibility” “Logic, Computation and Philosophy” “Notes on the Philosophy of Mathematics, March 1967” “Minds and Computers” “The Concept of Set” “Mathematical Notes” (Box 99, Folder 1389)
  - Notebook, "Literature, Medicine, Computers, Physics, etc.", 1984, 1985, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 1390)
  - Notebook, Logic Colloquium, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 1391)
  - Notebook, "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (1 of 2) (Box 100, Folder 1392)
  - Notebook, "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (2 of 2) (Box 100, Folder 1393)
  - Notebook, "An Logico-Historical Introduction to Math" (Box 100, Folder 1394)
  - Notebook, Manuscript, "From Mathematics to Philosophy (1 of 2) (Box 100, Folder 1395)
  - Notebook, Manuscript, "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (2 of 2) (Box 100, Folder 1396)
  - Notebook, Manuscript, "From Mathematics to Philosophy," Chapters VI-VIII (Box 101, Folder 1397)
  - Notebook, Manuscript, "From Mathematics to Philosophy," Chapters VII-XI, Origins of the Chapters, and Appendix (Box 101, Folder 1398)
  - Notebook, Manuscript, "From Mathematics to Philosophy," Chapters VIII-XI, Origins of the Chapters, Appendix (Box 101, Folder 1399)
  - Notebook, Manuscript, "Logic and Computation: Notes for Applied Math 232, Fall, 1966] (Box 101, Folder 1400)
  - Notebook, Manuscripts by Paul J. Cohen (Box 102, Folder 1401)
  - Notebook, Manuscripts and Notes, 1967-1968; Includes: “Tharp’s Book, Autumn, 1968” “Projective Hierarchy” “Über den Befriff der Definitheir in der Axiomatik” by Ernst Zermelo “The Axiom of Determinateness and Reduction Principles in the Analytical Hierarchy” by Donald A. Martin “Measurable Cardinals and Analytic Games” by Donald A. Martin “M. Rabin, October 19, 1967” “Solovay” “A Note on Singular Rowbottom Cardinals” by Eugene M. Kleinberg “Independence Results in Model Theory” by Robert Solovay, Notes by Eugene M. Kleinberg “Tharp – Set Theory, An Outline of Topics” “Tharp” (Box 102, Folder 1402)
  - Notebook, "I. Mathematical Concepts, II. Survey - A View of Mathematical Logic", 1959-1961 (Box 102, Folder 1403)
  - Notebook, Mathematical Logic for.../Simplified Mathematical Logic (Box 102, Folder 1404)
  - Notebook, Mathematical Logic Today/Tiling Problems/A Sketch of Mathematical Logic (Box 102, Folder 1405)
  - Notebook, "Mathematical Systems", 1955 (Box 102, Folder 1406)
  - Notebook, "Mathematical Theory of Calculating Machines, Symbiotic Logic, Statistics, and Calculating Machines" (Box 102, Folder 1407)
  - Notebook, "New Directions in Science and in Society: From Traditions to Innovations" and Supplemental Material, Includes: “On Computabilism and Physicalism: Some Subproblems” Excerpt from draft of MS “Shadows of the Mind” by Roger Penrose “The Seven World-Problems” by Emil du Bois-Reymond “The Limits of Our Knowledge of Nature” by Emil du Bois-Reymond (Box 103, Folder 1408)
  - Notebook, "Notes in Logic", 1977 (Box 103, Folder 1409)
  - Notebook, "Notes on Logic and Computers" (Box 103, Folder 1410)
  - Notebook, An Outline of Logic, Sketch of Math Logic (Box 103, Folder 1411)
  - Notebook, Paper on Newton's Geometry by Howard Stein (Box 103, Folder 1412)
  - Notebook, Philosophy 149 (Box 103, Folder 1413)
  - Notebook, "Philosophy", 1966-1967 (Box 103, Folder 1414)
  - Notebook, "Piano" (Box 104, Folder 1415)
  - Notebook, "Political Economy, Logical Problems of the World, Substantive Problems of Philosophy", 1979 (Box 104, Folder 1416)
  - Notebook, The Reading Group, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 1417)
  - Notebook, "Reflections on Kurt Gödel", 1985-1986 (Box 104, Folder 1418)
  - Notebook, "Separation and Combination, Marx and Before, Philosophical Problems" (Box 104, Folder 1419)
  - Notebook, "Set Theory - 1965" (Box 104, Folder 1420)
  - Notebook, Set Theory, Wang, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 1421)
  - Notebook, Some Problems of Knowledge, Knowledge and Logic Mathematics (Box 104, Folder 1422)
  - Notebook, "Sources of Modern Logic" (Box 104, Folder 1423)
  - Notebook, A Study of Philosophy and Computers with Mathematics as an Example (Box 105, Folder 1424)
  - Notebook, "A Survey of Mathematical Logic", 1959 (Box 105, Folder 1425)
  - Notebook, "A Synthesis of Math. Logic"/"Set Theory for the...", 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 1426)
  - Notebook, Teaching Notes, Philosophy of Science, 1951-1952 (Box 105, Folder 1427)
  - Notebook, "Theory of Meaning, Determinism and Causality" (Box 105, Folder 1428)
  - Notebook, "Thinking about Thinking", 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1429)
  - Notebook, Unlabeled (Box 105, Folder 1430)
  - Notebook, Unlabeled (Box 105, Folder 1431)
  - Notebook, Unlabeled (Box 105, Folder 1432)
  - Notebook, Unlabeled (Box 105, Folder 1433)
  - Notebook, Unlabeled (Box 106, Folder 1434)
  - Notebook, Unlabeled, 1962 (Box 106, Folder 1435)
  - Notebook, Unlabeled, 1962-1963 (Box 106, Folder 1436)
  - Notebook, Unlabeled, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 1437)
  - Notebook, Unlabeled Manuscripts, Includes: “Nested Recursion” by W.W. Tait “Finite Definability of Number-Theoretic Functions and Parametric Completeness of Equational Calculi” by G. Kreisel and W.W. Tait “Reflection Principles and Herbrand’s Theorem” “The Meaning of Brouwer’s Free Choice Sequences” “Completeness Problems for Intuitionist Mathematics” “Intuitionist Propositional Calculus” “Continuous Functionals of Finite Type. Applications.” “Applications of Mathematical Logic to Analytics Number Theory” “Theo Theorem of Artin” “Extensionality Conditions for Functionals of Type 3” “Ω-Closure and Presupposing the Totality of Natural Numbers” by G. Kreisel “Proposal for Research Project, Recursive Progressions of Theories” “Relative Interpretations” by Steven Orey (Box 106, Folder 1438)
  - Notebook, Unabeled Manuscripts (Box 107, Folder 1439)
  - Notebook, "Wang", 1966 (Box 107, Folder 1440)
  - Notebook, Wang, 1967 (Box 107, Folder 1441)
  - Notebooks, "Predicative Set Theory" (Box 107, Folder 1442)
  - Notebooks, Unlabeled, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 1443)
  - Notecards (Box 107, Folder 1444)
  - Notes, 1946-1948 (Box 108, Folder 1445)
  - Notes, "Aspects of Platonism," RC (Box 108, Folder 1446)
  - Notes by Dana Scott (Box 108, Folder 1447)
  - Notes from Summer of 1956 (Box 108, Folder 1448)
  - Notes, Math 223, 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 1449)
  - "Notes on a Class of Tiling Problems" (Box 108, Folder 1450)
  - Notes on Gödel, May-September, 1985, pgs. 102-200 (Box 108, Folder 1451)
  - Notes on History of Philosphy (1947) (Box 108, Folder 1452)
  - Notes on Intuitionism, Rec. for Thy., 1956 Summer and Before (Box 109, Folder 1453)
  - "Notes on Kant" by Margaret Wilson (Box 109, Folder 1454)
  - "Notes on Set Theory" (Box 109, Folder 1454A)
  - "Notes on the Justification of Induction" (Box 109, Folder 1455)
  - "Notes Related to Husserlian Themes" (Box 109, Folder 1456)
  - Notes, REM, CG: Reminders, July 1987 (Box 109, Folder 1457)
  - Notes, "The Conversations" (Box 109, Folder 1458)
  - Notes, Transparencies, Correspondence, and Manuscript by Palle Yourgrau (Box 109, Folder 1459)
  - "Objectivism of Sets and Concepts" (Box 109, Folder 1460)
  - "Of Philosophical Contraction: A Case Study from Russell to Quine" (Box 109, Folder 1461)
  - "Of Philosophical Contraction," Copy Sent to Henry Stanton (1 of 2), February 29, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 1462)
  - "Of Philosophical Contraction," Copy Sent to Henry Stanton (2 of 2), February 29, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 1463)
  - “The ω-Inconsistency of a Partial System of Set Theory” and “On the Consistency Question of Analysis” by Hao Wang (Box 110, Folder 1464)
  - "On Computabilism and Physicalism: Some Subproblems" (Box 110, Folder 1465)
  - "On Computabilism: Some Subproblems" (Box 110, Folder 1466)
  - "On Computabilism: Some Subproblems" (Box 110, Folder 1467)
  - "On Computabilism: Some Subproblems", 1993 (Box 110, Folder 1468)
  - "On Formal Undecidable Propositions of Principia mathematica and Related Systems I," Kurt Gödel, 1931; Includes: “Leven und Wirken Kurt Gödels” by Curt Christian (Box 110, Folder 1469)
  - “On Frege’s True Way Out – A New Approach to the Formalization of Naïve…” by Werner-Jimmy De Pouli-Schimonovich (Box 110, Folder 1470)
  - "On Perspicuous Objectivity: Discussions between Gödel and Wittgenstein", Includes: “Between Philosophy and Platonism in Mathematics, Discussions with Gödel and Wittgenstein” (Box 110, Folder 1471)
  - "On Perspicuous Objectivity: Discussions between Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 111, Folder 1472)
  - "On Physicalism and Algorithmism: Can Machines Think?" (Box 111, Folder 1473)
  - "On Saying What You Really Want to Say: Wittgenstein on Mathematics" by Juliet Floyd (Box 111, Folder 1474)
  - "On the Long-Range Prospects of Automatic Theorem-Proving" by Hao Wang (Box 111, Folder 1475)
  - "On the Löwenheim-Skolem Theorem", 1953 (Box 111, Folder 1476)
  - "On Undecidable Propositions of Formal Mathematical Systems," Notes on Lectures by Kurt Gödel, 1934 (Box 111, Folder 1477)
  - OPA, 7/1992, "On Physicalism and Algorithmism" (Box 111, Folder 1478)
  - Steven Orey (Box 111, Folder 1479)
  - Oxford (1 of 2), 1955-1961 (Box 111, Folder 1480)
  - Oxford (2 of 2), 1955-1961 (Box 112, Folder 1481)
  - P=NP?, Includes: “A Survey of Some Recent Results on Computational Complexity in Weak Theories of Arithmetic” by D.A. Joseph and P.R. Young “Feasible Computations and Provable Complexity Properties” by J. Hartmanis “The Horn Complexity of Boolean Functions and Cook’s Problem” by Stål O. Aanderaa and Egon Börger, 1979’ ‘Khachian’s Algorithm for Linear Programming” by Peter Gács and Laszlo Lovász “Soundness and Completeness of an Axiom System for Program Verification” by Stephen A. Cook “The Consistency of ‘P=NP’ and Related Problems with Fragments of Arithmetic” by Richard A. DeMillo and Richard J. Lipton (Box 112, Folder 1482)
  - P=NP?, Includes: “The Hardness of the Grid Problem Gi Under the Routine Resolution Method,” by Huang Wnqi, Lai Chusheng, and Chen Zhixiang “Hao Wang’s Contributions to Logic” by Wu Yuzeng “A Quasi-Physical Method for Solving the Covering Problem-An Approach to Tackling NP Hard Problem” by Huang Wenqi “Effective Transformations on Infinite Trees, with Applications to Hugh Undecidability, Dominoes, and Fairness” by David Harel “Fair Determination with Cruel Schedulers” by Ido Dayan and David Harel “Proving and Discovering Geometry Theorems using Wu’d Method” by Shang-ching Chou “A Collection of Geometry Theorems Proved Mechanically” by Shang-ching Chou “AIDS Programs” by Sue Walker Toledo (Box 112, Folder 1483)
  - Jari Palomäki (Box 112, Folder 1484)
  - Papers - Abstracts (Box 112, Folder 1485)
  - Papers by Kurt Gödel (Box 113, Folder 1486)
  - The Papers of Kurt Gödel: An Inventory (Box 113, Folder 1487)
  - Papers Related to "Survey", 1959 (Box 113, Folder 1488)
  - "Part III: The Concept of Number" (Box 113, Folder 1489)
  - George W. Patterson (Box 113, Folder 1490)
  - Pending (Box 113, Folder 1491)
  - Roger Penrose (Box 113, Folder 1492)
  - "Perspicuous Objectivity and Conceptual Realism" (Box 113, Folder 1493)
  - "Phenomenology and the Crisis of Philosophy" by Edmund Husserl (Box 113, Folder 1494)
  - "Philosophical Reflections on Gödel's Cosmology" by Palle Yourgrau (Box 113, Folder 1495)
  - Philosophy I (1947), Elementary Logic, Philosophy 3 (1947, Fall) (Box 113, Folder 1496)
  - "Philosophy and Our Need," 1990 (90MC) (Box 114, Folder 1497)
  - "Philosophy: Chinese and Western" (Box 114, Folder 1498)
  - "Philosophy: Chinese and Western" (Box 114, Folder 1499)
  - "Philosophy in America Today", 1981 (Box 114, Folder 1500)
  - Photocopied Manuscripts, Includes: “Die Widerspruchfeiheit der reinen Zahlentheorie” by Gerhard Gentzen “Neue Fassung des Widerspruchsfreiheitsbeweises für die reine Zahlentheorie” by Gerhard Gentzen (Box 114, Folder 1501)
  - "The Pinwheel Tilings of the Plane" and "Symmetry and Tilings" by Charles Radin (Box 114, Folder 1502)
  - PMABC, "Powers of the Mind: Above Brains and Computers" (Box 114, Folder 1503)
  - PMABC, June 14, 1993, "Preparations for Minds above Brains and Computers" (Box 114, Folder 1504)
  - PMABC (continued), 93-94, "Time in Philosophy and in Physics - From Kant and Einstein to Gödel", 1993-1994 (Box 115, Folder 1505)
  - PMP, "Purity of Mind" (Box 115, Folder 1506)
  - PMP, 7/1992, "Purity of Mind: Philosophy through Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 115, Folder 1507)
  - Popular Lectures and MS, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 1508)
  - "Popular Lectures in Mathematical Logic" (Italian Translation) (Box 115, Folder 1509)
  - "Popular Lectures on Mathematical Logic" (1 of 2) (Box 115, Folder 1510)
  - "Popular Lectures on Mathematical Logic" (2 of 2) (Box 115, Folder 1511)
  - "Popular Lectures on Mathematical Logic," Postscript (Box 116, Folder 1512)
  - “Prädikative Klassen” by Ralf-Dieter Schindler (Box 116, Folder 1513)
  - Preface, Table of Contents (Box 116, Folder 1514)
  - Printed Matter (Box 116, Folder 1515)
  - PRN, "Philosophy and Our Real Mind," "Philosophy and Our Real Need" (Box 116, Folder 1516)
  - "Problems and Solutions," Inserts for Xerox Copies (Box 116, Folder 1517)
  - "Process and Reality in Mathematics" (Box 116, Folder 1518)
  - "Programming Logic and Program Correctness Proof" by Feng Yu-lin (Box 116, Folder 1519)
  - PTML, "Philosophy through Mathematics and Logic" (Box 116, Folder 1520)
  - PUM1 and Lcg, Gödel-related (Box 116, Folder 1521)
  - PuM1, Chapter 1, "Philosophies and Philosophers," 6/1992 (Box 116, Folder 1522)
  - Purity (1983), "The Pursuit of Purity by Wittgenstein, Gödel, Quine" (Box 117, Folder 1523)
  - "Purity II" (Box 117, Folder 1524)
  - "Purity," Gödel-Wittgenstein (Box 117, Folder 1525)
  - "Purity is Not Enough"/"The Pursuit of Purity by Wittgenstein, Gödel, and Quine" (Box 117, Folder 1526)
  - Purity is Not Enough, Notes on Paradoxes (Box 117, Folder 1527)
  - "Purity," "KG - Kurt Gödel - and Some of his Philosophical Views" (Box 117, Folder 1528)
  - "Purity," "Objectivism of Sets and Concepts" (Box 117, Folder 1529)
  - "Purity of the Mind" (Box 117, Folder 1530)
  - "Purity of the Mind: Philosophy Through Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 117, Folder 1531)
  - "Purity," Quine (Box 117, Folder 1532)
  - "Purity," Wittgenstein, Chronological Table (Box 117, Folder 1533)
  - "Quine" by Burton Dreben (Box 117, Folder 1534)
  - Quine, Math 19A, 1947 (Box 118, Folder 1535)
  - Quine - References and Chronology (Box 118, Folder 1536)
  - "Quine's Logical Ideas and Philosophical Presuppositions in Historical Perspective" (Box 118, Folder 1537)
  - "Quine's Logical Ideas and Philosophical Presuppositions in Historical Perspective" (Final) (Box 118, Folder 1538)
  - "Quine's Logical Ideas and Philosophical Presuppositions in Historical Perspective" (Handscript) (Box 118, Folder 1539)
  - "Quine's Logical Ideas and Philosophical Presuppositions in Historical Perspective" (Spare Sheets) (Box 118, Folder 1540)
  - "Quine's Logical Ideas and Philosophical Presuppositions in Historical Perspective" (Working Xerox Copy) (1 of 2) (Box 118, Folder 1541)
  - "Quine's Logical Ideas and Philosophical Presuppositions in Historical Perspective" (Working Xerox Copy) (2 of 2) (Box 119, Folder 1542)
  - "Quine's Logical Ideas and Philosophical Presuppositions in Historical Perspective" (Xerox Copies - Final) (Box 119, Folder 1543)
  - "Quine's Logical Ideas in Historical Perspectives," Critique (Box 119, Folder 1544)
  - Tibor Rado (Box 119, Folder 1545)
  - "Random Notes on Tussell and an Essay on His Logic" (Box 119, Folder 1546)
  - RE Models (Box 119, Folder 1547)
  - "The Reconstruction of Mathematics" (Box 119, Folder 1548)
  - Reducibility (Box 119, Folder 1549)
  - “Reduktionstheorie des Entscheidungsproblems im Prädikatenkalkül der ersten Stufe nach der Methode von Kahr-Moore-Wang” and“Untersuchungen zum entscheidungsproblem im Prädikatenkalkül der ersten Stufe” by Jürgen Genenz (Box 119, Folder 1550)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel" (Box 120, Folder 1551)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel, and Varieties of Rationalistic Optimism" and "Reflections on Kurt Gödel (and the Tasks of Philosophy)":, 1985 (Box 120, Folder 1552)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel," Corrections for Future Editions (Box 120, Folder 1553)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel," Correspondence, etc. (Box 120, Folder 1554)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel," Edited Manuscript (1 of 2), October 7, 1986 (Box 121, Folder 1555)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel," Edited Manuscript (2 of 2), October 7, 1986 (Box 121, Folder 1556)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel," Office Copy (1 of 2), June 26, 1985 (Box 121, Folder 1557)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel," Office Copy (2 of 2), June 26, 1986 (Box 121, Folder 1558)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel," Reviews (Box 122, Folder 1559)
  - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel," Uncorrected (Box 122, Folder 1560)
  - "A Refutation Procedure and Its Model - Theoretic Justification" by John Denton, Burton Dreben, and Hao Wang (Box 122, Folder 1561)
  - "Remarks on Constructive Ordinals and Set Theory" by Hao Wang (Box 122, Folder 1562)
  - "Remarks on Philosophy: Its Nature and Place", 1981 (Box 122, Folder 1563)
  - Report for Philosophy 14, "The Idea of Universal Mathematics in 17th Century Philosophy", Autumn 1946 (Box 122, Folder 1564)
  - "Report No. BL-37, Theory of Switching" by the Staff of the Harvard University Computation Laboratory to Bell Telephone Laboratories, 1964 (Box 122, Folder 1565)
  - Reviews and Remarks on Wang's Books (Box 122, Folder 1566)
  - Reviews - Hao Wang's Books (Box 122, Folder 1567)
  - Reviews (mostly of "RG" - "Reflections on Kurt Gödel) (Box 122, Folder 1568)
  - "The Rightful Place of Mathematics in Philosophy" by Hao Wang, and Notes (Box 122, Folder 1569)
  - Guy Robinson (Box 123, Folder 1570)
  - N.A. Routledge (Box 123, Folder 1571)
  - J. Philip Rubenstein (Box 123, Folder 1572)
  - Russell, etc., Brown, Cook, 1966; Includes: “Logic and Foundations Lectures,” 1966 “The Unity of Knowledge,” 1968 “Existence and Quantification” by W.V. Quine “On Russell’s Phenomenological Constructionism” by Carl G. Hempel “Russell and Philosophy” “Russell’s Ontological Development” by W.V. Quine “Short Definitions of the Class of Ordinals” by Kenneth R. Brown and Hao Wang “Natural Hulls and Set Existence” “A Note on Finite Ordinals” “Finite Set Theory, Number Theory and Axioms of Limitation” by Kenneth R. Brown and Hao Wang “Remarks on Machines, Sets, and the Decision Problem” by Hao Wang “An Analysis of Herbrand’s Dissertation” “On the Property C” by Stål O. Aanderaa (Box 123, Folder 1573)
  - Kurt Schütte (Box 123, Folder 1574)
  - Scientific American Article, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 1575)
  - Scientific American, "Gödel and Einstein as Companions" (Box 123, Folder 1576)
  - Scrapbook of Gödel-related Material (Box 123, Folder 1577)
  - Script for "Kurt Gödel: Ein Mathematischer Mythos" by Peter Weibel and Werner Schimanovich (Box 123, Folder 1578)
  - John R. Searle (Box 124, Folder 1579)
  - Second Edition, "A Survey of Mathematical Logic", Includes: “Introduction to the Second Edition” “Tharp and Conceptual Logic” (Box 124, Folder 1580)